[
    {
        "Question": "doctrine",
        "Answer": "principle",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "momentous",
        "Answer": "very important",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "lure",
        "Answer": "attract",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ensue",
        "Answer": "result",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "boundary",
        "Answer": "periphery",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "advocated",
        "Answer": "promoted",
        "Options": "proponents"
    },
    {
        "Question": "flaw",
        "Answer": "fault",
        "Options": "incorrect"
    },
    {
        "Question": "lavishly",
        "Answer": "richly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "highlights",
        "Answer": "emphasizes",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "marginally",
        "Answer": "slightly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "foul",
        "Answer": "pollute",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "compression",
        "Answer": "crushing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "array",
        "Answer": "range",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "scarcity",
        "Answer": "lack",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "location",
        "Answer": "place",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "subsistence",
        "Answer": "survival",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "the application of waterpower",
        "Answer": "the uses to which waterpower was put",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "simultaneously",
        "Answer": "at the same time",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "significant",
        "Answer": "considerable",
        "Options": "important"
    },
    {
        "Question": "alarm",
        "Answer": "sound",
        "Options": "warning"
    },
    {
        "Question": "augment",
        "Answer": "increase",
        "Options": "supplement"
    },
    {
        "Question": "prediction",
        "Answer": "expectation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "engage in",
        "Answer": "involve in",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intact",
        "Answer": "undamaged",
        "Options": "whole"
    },
    {
        "Question": "conversely",
        "Answer": "on the other hand",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "overwhelming",
        "Answer": "powerful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "representative",
        "Answer": "typical",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "suppress",
        "Answer": "stop by force",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "logical",
        "Answer": "reasonable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "convergence",
        "Answer": "gathering",
        "Options": "concentrating"
    },
    {
        "Question": "function",
        "Answer": "purpose",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intense",
        "Answer": "extreme",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "surpass",
        "Answer": "exceed",
        "Options": "be higher than"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compelled",
        "Answer": "required",
        "Options": "push"
    },
    {
        "Question": "hemispheres",
        "Answer": "sides",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "encompasses",
        "Answer": "includes",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "coalesced",
        "Answer": "joined",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "rival",
        "Answer": "competing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "reasonable",
        "Answer": "sufficient",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pioneering",
        "Answer": "original/ introduced",
        "Options": "leader"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dependable",
        "Answer": "reliable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "clear",
        "Answer": "visible",
        "Options": "apparrent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "eccentric",
        "Answer": "strange",
        "Options": "erratic"
    },
    {
        "Question": "remote",
        "Answer": "distant",
        "Options": "isolated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "trivial",
        "Answer": "small",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "critically",
        "Answer": "fundamentally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "comparably",
        "Answer": "similarly",
        "Options": "equivalently"
    },
    {
        "Question": "absorb",
        "Answer": "appeal",
        "Options": "learn/ take in"
    },
    {
        "Question": "impetus",
        "Answer": "motivation",
        "Options": "incentive/ stimulus"
    },
    {
        "Question": "congeal",
        "Answer": "solidify",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accomplished",
        "Answer": "achieved",
        "Options": "skilled"
    },
    {
        "Question": "at random",
        "Answer": "without a definite pattern",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "proximity",
        "Answer": "closeness",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "assured",
        "Answer": "guaranteed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accustomed to",
        "Answer": "became used to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "apart from",
        "Answer": "besides",
        "Options": "except for"
    },
    {
        "Question": "consult",
        "Answer": "ask",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "coated",
        "Answer": "layer",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "diversification",
        "Answer": "emergence of many varieties",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "impervious to",
        "Answer": "unaffected by",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "appealing",
        "Answer": "attractive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "crushed",
        "Answer": "ground",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "moral",
        "Answer": "lesson",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "indispensable",
        "Answer": "essential",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "abort",
        "Answer": "quit",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mandated",
        "Answer": "required",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mundane",
        "Answer": "ordinary",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "evident",
        "Answer": "obvious",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deceiving",
        "Answer": "misleading",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "discern",
        "Answer": "identify",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "convict",
        "Answer": "sentence",
        "Options": "condemn"
    },
    {
        "Question": "commemorate",
        "Answer": "celebrate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "constellation",
        "Answer": "colleciton",
        "Options": "combination"
    },
    {
        "Question": "improve",
        "Answer": "refine",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "leftover",
        "Answer": "remaining",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "application",
        "Answer": "use",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "relics",
        "Answer": "remains",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "coupled with",
        "Answer": "combined with",
        "Options": "associated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "decorating",
        "Answer": "ornamental",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "adjacent to",
        "Answer": "next to/ nearby",
        "Options": "neighboring"
    },
    {
        "Question": "ethic",
        "Answer": "set of moral principles",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dispersed",
        "Answer": "scattered",
        "Options": "spread"
    },
    {
        "Question": "fractures",
        "Answer": "cracks",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accomodate",
        "Answer": "provide for",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mechanisms of natural selection",
        "Answer": "ways natural selection works",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "disgust",
        "Answer": "distaste",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "imitate",
        "Answer": "copy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "raw",
        "Answer": "uncooked",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "anticipate",
        "Answer": "expect",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "approximating",
        "Answer": "estimating",
        "Options": "resembling"
    },
    {
        "Question": "derive",
        "Answer": "gain",
        "Options": "obtain"
    },
    {
        "Question": "overlie",
        "Answer": "cover",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "virtually",
        "Answer": "almost/ nearly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inherent",
        "Answer": "built-in",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "instigate",
        "Answer": "caused",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "precisely",
        "Answer": "exactly",
        "Options": "accurately"
    },
    {
        "Question": "crest",
        "Answer": "peak",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "is usually accompanied by",
        "Answer": "usually occurs together with",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dismantle",
        "Answer": "demolish",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ingested",
        "Answer": "eaten",
        "Options": "swallowed"
    }
]